[{"answer": "Who is he", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What are you doing", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What you reading", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What's your name? Catcher", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I went to the doctor. He says I'm fertile. He says I could repopulate the entire planet", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "He didn't say", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Twenty two", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "How old are you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "How old are you", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Not aolt to look at. What are your folks like", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "My husband doesn't get me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I've seen better, I've seen worse. Nah. That's why I ain't never married. You got yourself the best fish in the sea", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "If I was a woman, I'd be a slut. A lesbian slut", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No thank you", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well where is he", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm gonna let you off here, okay", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yeah, you know what I'm gonna do? I'm gonna park the car, then I'm gonna meet you inside", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Not very light is it", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I heard it was the couple that lays together stays together", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Saw me what", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I don't care. I'm not in the mood", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Why? Beacause we forgot our Bibles is why", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I thought you said we'd go today", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I thought you said we'd go today", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What came up", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Um, okay. I think, maybe, somebody's found out about us", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Well, maybe I don't get you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It's my friend.", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You've never done it on your own", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "A blind man can go deaf. A widow can lose her children. Babies starve and they never get food. They never get any food. They just come into the world and they die", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I can't calm down! I'd be easy if I was a hooker like you. I could calm down all over town", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Calm down, my friend", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Hey, hey! I am not a hooker", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "The little plastic doohickey's turnin' blue. What's that mean", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Bright blue", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "No, I'm excited. It's just, a lot of worries come with havin' a baby..", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Do you think anything's gonna change havin' a baby", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Don't think negative. Think positive. We could have ourselves a tiny my friend. Or a tiny Teeny. Teeny's gonna have a tiny weeny Teeny", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What do you mean? Everything's gonna change", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Do you think anything's gonna change havin' a baby", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yeah, but I mean, do you think anything's really gonna change", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What do you mean? Everything's gonna change", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What do ya mean", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "No. I don't know anything", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I hardly know him", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I can't go tonight. I gotta pack my things and I'd have to get more money", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "This is all going too fast", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Why? Why", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Don't you love me? Don't you love me at all", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, my friend", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Okay. Get stoned", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I need to get stoned", "docId": "Good-Girl_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I just gotta escape, you know. You ever feel like that? Like you gotta escape", "qsentId": 56}]